[Music]
This is the biggest national issue,
I am brother, Banda Banda Banda Banda Banda, I
came and saved him, one one one one one one Banda
Banda Banda Tapa, he
said, my exit,
stand in front of this
[Music]
Habibi, welcome to Dubai,
Habibi, welcome to Dubai, Habibi, welcome to Dubai, Habibi, welcome to Habibi, come
to Dubai,
hey
Dubai, okay let's go
[Music]
Los
Hal Va [
Music]
Aa
[Music]
Yesterday, yes, they showed us the desert safari.   It
was ultimate.  Today, whatever has brought us here, we have
brought it to the one to four floor.  It
is a very nice view.  We are feeling very good.
Thanks to My Size Smart.
Hot tere banner ni
chhapte tere banner neer ni
hot tere banner ni chhapte tere banner ni
fashion tu karti jive kali channel ni munda
thakta nahi
ici no maar for giving us this
opportunity to us we are very happy we are very
happy and satisfied thank you
so much we are
at burj khalifa
[music]
zikr dila doon teu bur khalifa tenu bur
khalifa o tenu bur khalifa tenu bur khalifa o
tenu bur khalifa
hai
[music]
thank you.   India is
not a name, it is a celebration The habit of winning is in our blood
Such a skill Even the enemy salutes
you Sun, we are your light We will not part from you till the
end Companions of the tricolor who are
in every vein Every game is in the control of
India
Shyamala Vande Mataram
[Music]
Shyam Vande Mataram
This is the first time I have come here
but after seeing it I feel that the cleanliness, the
culture and the
great example of architecture that one gets to see
After seeing this I feel that if all the people are
sent to ICICI Labord here, they will get
inspired here
Congratulations bro
Thank you new car Hi
about a new Ferrari This is cross
together from today It's my car.
Congratulations, thank you, thank you, this is the
first car.  I am buying Ferrari.  Thank you very much.
From ICICI I am buying this car.
Everyone hey
bowls what should I do
all night what should I do
all night what should I do all night what should I do
all night what should I do all night
Om
[Music]